

KIERAN VIEIRA

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

e. Kieranviena@nve.com
w: www.kieranvieira.com
SOCIAL —
witter.com/kirovieira
in linkedin.com/in/kieran-vieira/
instagram.com/vieiraillustration
SKILLS —
Photoshop
HTML5
CSS
Pre-Processors Pre-Processors
React.js
WordPress (CMS)
Communication
Problem Solving Problem Solving
Teamwork
Creativity
HOBBIES —

CONTACT

A. kioranvioira@livo.com

t: 1 289 697 2134

ABOUT

I have been doing Graphic Design for almost a decade now specializing in improving user experience. I have been focusing on Web Development for the past 3 years and am currently enrolled in Lambda School's Full Stack Web Development program where I've expanded my tech stack to include many modern technologies.

EDUCATION

COMPUTER SCIENCE / FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT Lambda School | California | 2018 - 2019

AN MYER SECONDARY

Niagara Falls, Ontario | 2013 - 2017

EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPER

Vieira Illustration | Freelance | 2016 - Present

I have been doing freelance Web Development for multiple companies and creators for a couple years now and have been improving my skills with every project. Visit the website for more information http://vieiraillustration.com

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Vieira Illustration | Freelance | 2015 - Present

I've done multiple freelance designs, business cards, and logos for some well-known local companies to help with branding and company reach using Google Analytics, Google Business, Google AdWords, and WordPress for social management.

STORE MANAGER / PIZZA CHEF

G'z Pizza and Wings | Niagara Falls, Ontario | 2017 - 2018

Managed in store day to day tasks such as stocking store, managing online ordering/party orders, ensuring quality of food, customer service, and opening/closing store. Provided detailed reports on business analytics to maintain quality for the customers and franchise.

I am very interested in all forms of art Music | Movies | Photography | Illustration